http://www.snowbird.com/privacy/

Snowbird Privacy Policy
Last Revised: July 20, 2020;
Effective Date: July 20, 2020
This website is owned and operated by Snowbird Resort, LLC, a Utah ski resort. This Privacy Policy describes how Snowbird Resort, LLC (“Snowbird,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) collects, uses, shares, and safeguards personal information. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your personal information, and how you can reach us to get answers to your questions. You can jump to particular topics by going to the headings below: This website is owned and operated by Snowbird Resort, LLC, a Utah ski resort. This Privacy Policy describes how Snowbird Resort, LLC (“Snowbird,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) collects, uses, shares, and safeguards personal information. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your personal information, and how you can reach us to get answers to your questions.  You can jump to particular topics by going to the headings below:
Types Of Information We Collect
Use And Processing Of Information
Sharing Of Information
Your Choices
How We Protect Personal Information
Our Online Privacy Policy for Children
Miscellaneous
Contact Information
Types Of Information We Collect
The following provides examples of the type of information that we collect from you and how we use that information.
Context
Types of Data
Primary Purpose for Collection and Use of Data
Account Registration and Program Enrollment
We collect your name and contact information when you create an account or enroll for a program.  We also collect information relating to the actions that you perform while logged into your account.
We use the information collected when you create an account or enroll in a program to perform our contract to provide you with products or services. We also have a legitimate interest in providing account related functionalities to our users. Accounts can be used for easy checkout and to save your preferences and transaction history.
Client Information
We collect the name, and contact information, of our clients and their employees with whom we may interact.
We use this information to perform our contract with clients by communicating with them concerning normal business administration such as projects, services, and billing.
Competition Entry
We collect your name and contact information when you enter into a competition.
We use the information collected when you enter into a competition to perform our contractual obligations. We also have a legitimate interest in organizing our events.
Cookies and first party tracking
We use cookies and clear GIFs. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website sends to a computer’s hard drive while a web site is viewed...
We have a legitimate interest in making our website operate efficiently.
Cookies and Third Party Tracking
We participate in behavior-based advertising, this means that a third party uses technology (e.g., a cookie) to collect information about your use of our website so that they can provide advertising about products and services tailored to your interests on our website, or on other websites.
We have a legitimate interest in engaging in behavior-based advertising and capturing website analytics.
Demographic Information
We collect personal information, such as your age, physical characteristics, or location.
In some cases, we use this information to perform our contracts to provide you with products or services. We also have a legitimate interest in understanding our users and providing tailored services.
Distance Information
When you use one of our Apps we collect your location from the GPS, Wi-Fi, and/or cellular technology in your device to determine your location and your distance from a store that sells our products.
We have a legitimate interest in understanding our users and providing tailored services.  In some contexts our use is also based upon your consent to provide us with geo location information.
Email Interconnectivity
If you receive email from us, we use certain tools to capture data related to when you open our message, click on any links or banners it contains and make purchases.
We use the information collected when you create an account or enroll in a program to perform our contract to provide you with products or services. We also have a legitimate interest in providing account related functionalities to our users. Accounts can be used for easy checkout and to save your preferences and transaction history.
Employment
If you apply for a job posting or enter into employment with us we collect information necessary to process your application or to retain you as an employee. Providing this information is required for employment.
We use this information about you in anticipation of a contract of employment with you. In some contexts, we are also required by law to collect information about our employees. We also have a legitimate interest in using your information to have efficient staffing and work force operations.
Feedback/Support
If you provide us feedback or contact us for support we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content that you send to us, in order to reply.
We have a legitimate interest in receiving, and acting upon, your feedback or issues. In some cases, we may use this information to perform our contract with you.
Mailing List
When you sign up for one of our mailing lists we collect your email address or postal address.
We share information about our products and services with individuals that consent to receive such information. We also have a legitimate interest in sharing information about our products or services.
Mobile Devices
We collect information from your mobile device such as unique identifying information broadcast from your device when visiting our website or when visiting one of our resorts.
We have a legitimate interest in identifying unique visitors, and in understanding how users interact with us on their mobile devices.
Order Placement
We collect your name, billing address, shipping address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card number when you place an order.
We use your information to perform our contract to provide you with products or services.
Partner and Sponsor Promotion
We collect information that you provide as part of a co-branded promotion with another company and events sponsored by another company.
We have a legitimate interest in fulfilling our promotions. In many cases we use this information with your consent.
Photographs
We collect photographs that you provide to us.
We collect photographs from individuals who give us their consent. We also have a legitimate interest in confirming your identity when you visit our resorts.
Posting in Public Forums
We collect the information you provide to us through our online forum, The Bird’s Nest.
We have a legitimate interest in understanding your opinions and to provide a forum for discussion, asking questions, posting photos and reviews, and sharing experiences
Spa and Resort Reservations
We collect your contact information, payment information, reservation information, and accommodation preferences. That information is collected directly from you when you make a reservation. In a small number of cases we collect information about a guest’s health. For example, a guest may voluntarily choose to provide information about a disability as part of a request for an accommodation preference.
We use your information in order to perform our contractual obligations, fulfill your requests for a reservation, and to take steps in anticipation of those obligations. In some jurisdictions we also need your information to comply with legal obligations to collect and maintain information about guests. We also have a legitimate interest in analyzing trends and patterns among guests. In the rare circumstances in which we collect information about a guest’s health, that information is collected only for the purpose of accommodating a guest’s needs and is used for no other purpose.
Surveys
When you participate in a survey we collect information that you provide through the survey. If the survey is provided by a third party service provider, the third party’s privacy policy applies to the collection, use, and disclosure of your information.
We have a legitimate interest in understanding your opinions, and collecting information relevant to our organization.
Sweepstakes or contests
When you participate in a sweepstakes or contest we collect information about you which includes contact information to notify you if you are selected.
We have a legitimate interest in operating the sweepstakes. In some contexts we are also required by law to collect information about those that enter into our sweepstakes, and we have a legitimate interest in complying with those laws.
Website interactions
We use technology to monitor how you interact with our website. This may include which links you click on, or information that you type into our online forms. This may also include information about your device or browser.
We have a legitimate interest in understanding how you interact with our website to better improve it, and to understand your preferences and interests in order to select offerings that you might find most useful. We also have a legitimate interest in detecting and preventing fraud.
Web logs
We collect information, including your browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to a computer when the Internet is used), domain name, click-activity, referring website, and/or a date/time stamp for visitors.
We have a legitimate interest in monitoring our networks and the visitors to our websites. Among other things, it helps us understand which of our services is the most popular.
In addition to the information that we collect from you directly, we may also receive information about you from other sources, including third parties, business partners, our affiliates, or publicly available sources. For example, if you submit a job application, or become an employee, we may conduct a background check.
Use and Processing of Information
In addition to the purposes and uses described above, we use information in the following ways:
Provide you with the best customer experience possible;
Provide the products and services you purchase, and to respond to your questions;
Communicate with you regarding purchases, registrations, offers, snow/terrain conditions, special events, and promotions;
Deliver customized content and advertising that may be of interest to you, and remember you when you visit our Sites;
Address network integrity and security issues;
Evaluate online job applications and respond to your inquiries into potential employment;
Respond to your requests, questions, and/or comments;
Perform data analyses (including market and consumer research, and trend analyses).
To identify you when you visit our websites or our resorts.
To streamline the checkout process.
To send marketing materials that may relate to our products, services, sales, or promotions, or those of our business partners.
For internal administrative purposes, as well as to manage our relationships.
Although the sections above describe our primary purpose in collecting your information, in many situations we have more than one purpose.  For example, if you complete an online purchase we may collect your information to perform our contract with you, but we also collect your information as we have a legitimate interest in maintaining your information after your transaction is complete so that we can quickly and easily respond to any questions about your order.  As a result, our collection and processing of your information is based in different contexts upon your consent, our need to perform a contract, our obligations under law, and/or our legitimate interest in conducting our business.
Sharing Of Information
Snowbird does not sell, lease, or rent your Personal Information. In addition to the specific situations discussed elsewhere in this policy, we disclose information in the following situations:
Affiliates and Acquisitions. We may share information with our corporate affiliates (e.g., parent company, sister companies, subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control).  If another company acquires, or plans to acquire, our company, business, or our assets, we will also share information with that company, including at the negotiation stage.
Other Disclosures with Your Consent. We may ask if you would like us to share your information with other unaffiliated third parties who are not described elsewhere in this policy.
Other Disclosures without Your Consent. We may disclose information in response to subpoenas, warrants, or court orders, or in connection with any legal process, or to comply with relevant laws.  We may also share your information in order to establish or exercise our rights, to defend against a legal claim, to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible illegal activities, suspected fraud, safety of person or property, or a violation of our policies, or to comply with your request for the shipment of products to or the provision of services by a third party intermediary.
Public. Some of our websites may provide the opportunity to post comments, or reviews, in a public forum. If you decide to submit information on these pages, that information may be publically available. When you use the Bird’s Nest, the information that you share may be collected by other visitors. We do not provide any type of security or protection for information that you provide in The Bird’s Nest. Information concerning the policies and procedures that govern The Bird’s Nest is available on the website. We reserve the right to censor information that we deem to be distasteful, harmful or otherwise inappropriate on The Bird’s Nest.
Partner Promotion. We may offer contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions with third party partners. If you decide to enter a contest, sweepstakes, or promotion that is sponsored by a third party partner the information that you provide will be shared with us and with them.  Their use of your information is not governed by this privacy policy.
Service Providers. We share your information with service providers.  Among other things service providers help us to administer our website, conduct surveys, provide technical support, process payments, and assist in the fulfillment of orders.
Your Choices
You can make the following choices regarding your personal information:
Access To Your Personal Information. You may request access to your personal information by contacting us at the address described below. If required by law, upon request, we will grant you reasonable access to the personal information that we have about you.  In certain circumstances, we will provide this information in a portable format. Note that California residents may be entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information (if any) we share with third parties or affiliates for direct marketing.
Changes To Your Personal Information. We rely on you to update and correct your personal information.  Most of our websites allow you to modify or delete your account profile.  If our website does not permit you to update or correct certain information, you contact us at the address described below in order to request that your information by modified. Note that we may keep historical information in our backup files as permitted by law.
Deletion Of Your Personal Information. Typically we retain your personal information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this policy, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.  You may, however, request information about how long we keep a specific type of information, or request that we delete your personal information by contacting us at the address described below.  If required by law we will grant a request to delete information, but you should note that in many situations we must keep your personal information to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements, or for another one of our business purposes.
Objection to Certain Processing. You may object to our use or disclosure of your personal information by contacting us at the address described below.
Online Tracking. We do not currently recognize automated browser signals regarding tracking mechanisms, which may include "Do Not Track" instructions.
Promotional Emails. You may choose to provide us with your email address for the purpose of allowing us to send free newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials to you, as well as targeted offers from third parties. You may choose to opt-out or unsubscribe by going to the  Email Preference Center or by sending an email to  info@snowbird.com . Each time we contact you via email using your personal information, we will offer you an opportunity to opt-out or unsubscribe, either entirely or for specific purposes. Please note that our online subscription database is for email marketing programs only. To opt-out from all communications including direct mail, please change your preferences by sending an email to  info@snowbird.com .
Promotional Mailings. If at any time you do not want to receive offers and/or circulars from us you can remove yourself from our mailing lists by emailing us (our contact information is below) with "NO SNAIL MAIL" in the subject line along with your name, address and zip code. Please note that our mailings are prepared in advance of their being sent. Although we will remove your name from our mailing list after receiving your request, you may still receive mailings from us that had been initiated prior to your name being removed.
Promotional Text Messages. If you receive a text message from us that contains promotional information you can opt-out of receiving future text messages by replying “STOP.”
Revocation Of Consent. If you revoke your consent for the processing of personal information then we may no longer be able to provide you services. In some cases, we may limit or deny your request to revoke consent if the law permits or requires us to do so, or if we are unable to adequately verify your identity. You may revoke consent to processing (where such processing is based upon consent) by contacting us at the address described below.
Please address written requests and questions about your rights to info@snowbird.com Attn: Database Marketing Manager or call us at 1.800.232.9542.
Note that, as required by law, we will require you to prove your identity.  We may conduct an identity verification by phone call or email. Depending on your request, we will ask for information such as your name, email, phone number, the last item you purchased from us, or the date of your last purchase from us. We may also ask you to provide a signed declaration confirming your identity. Following a request, we will use reasonable efforts to supply, correct or delete personal information about you in our files.
In some circumstances, you may designate an authorized agent to submit requests to exercise certain privacy rights on your behalf.  We will require verification that you provided the authorized agent permission to make a request on your behalf.  You must provide us with a copy of the signed permission you have given to the authorized agent to submit the request on your behalf and verify your own identity directly with us.
Information for Authorized Agents
If you are an authorized agent submitting a request on behalf of an individual you must attach a copy of the following information to the request:
A completed Authorized Agent Designation Form indicating that you have authorization to act on the consumer’s behalf. Please email info@snowbird.com to request the Authorized Agent Designation Form.
If you are a business, proof that you are registered with the Secretary of State to conduct business in California.
If we do not receive both pieces of information, the request will be denied.
How We Protect Personal Information
No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is fully secure. While we use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information. In the event that we are required by law to inform you of a breach to your personal information we may notify you electronically, in writing, or by telephone, if permitted to do so by law.
Some of our websites permit you to create an account. When you do you will be prompted to create a password.  You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password, and you are responsible for any access to or use of your account by someone else that has obtained your password, whether or not such access or use has been authorized by you.  You should notify us of any unauthorized use of your password or account.
Our Online Privacy Policy for Children
We are concerned about the safety of children and will comply, at all times, with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. Accordingly, we do not knowingly collect email subscription information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have email subscription information on a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information from our systems as soon as we discover that it has been submitted it and we will not disclose it to third parties.
Other Important Information
The following additional information relates to our privacy practices:
Transmission Of Information To Other Countries. Your information may be processed in a foreign country where privacy laws may be less stringent than the laws in your country.  Nonetheless, where possible we take steps to treat personal information using the same privacy principles that apply pursuant to the law of the country in which we first received your information.  By submitting your personal information to us you agree to the transfer, storage and processing of your information in a country other than your country of residence including, but not necessarily limited to, the United States.  If you would like more information concerning our attempts to apply the privacy principles applicable in one jurisdiction to data when it goes to another jurisdiction you can contact us using the contact information below.
Third Party Applications/Websites.  Our website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of other web sites. We encourage you to note when you leave our site and to read the privacy policies listed on these (and all) third party sites. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected on Snowbird’s website. If you choose to provide information on a third party site, that information will be subject to that party's privacy policy.
Changes To This Privacy Policy. Snowbird reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. To the extent that our policy changes in a material way, the policy that was in place at the time that you submitted personal information to us will generally govern that information unless we receive your consent to the new privacy policy.  Our privacy policy includes an “effective” and “last updated” date. The effective date refers to the date that the current version took effect. The last updated date refers to the date that the current version was last substantively modified.
Information for California Residents. California Civil Code Sections 1798.115(c), 1798.130(a)(5)(c), 1798.130(c), and 1798.140 indicate that organizations should disclose whether certain categories of information are collected, “sold” or transferred for an organization’s “business purpose”(as those terms are defined under California law).  You can find a list of the categories of information that we collect and share here. Please note that because this list is comprehensive it may refer to types of information that we share about people other than yourself. If you would like more information concerning the categories of personal information (if any) we share with third parties or affiliates for those parties to use for direct marketing please submit a written request to us using the information in the "Contact Information" section below.  We do not discriminate against California residents who exercise any of their rights described in this Privacy Policy.
Contact Information
If you have any questions, comments, or complaints concerning our privacy practices please contact us at the appropriate address below.  We will attempt to respond to your requests and to provide you with additional privacy-related information.
Email
info@snowbird.com
Mail
3165 East Millrock Drive, Suite 150
Holladay, UT 84121-5571
Phone
1.800.232.9542
If you are not satisfied with our response, and are in the European Union, you may have a right to lodge a complaint with your local supervisory authority.
California Information Sharing Disclosure
California Civil Code Sections 1798.115(c), 1798.130(a)(5)(c), 1798.130(c), and 1798.140 indicate that organizations should disclose whether the following categories of personal information are collected, transferred for “valuable consideration,” or transferred for an organization’s “business purpose” (as those terms are defined under California law).  The table below indicates the categories of personal information we collect and transfer in a variety of contexts.  Please note that because this list is comprehensive, it may refer to types of information that we collect and share about people other than yourself.  For example, while we transfer credit card or debit card numbers for our business purpose in order to process payments for orders placed with us, we do not collect or transfer credit card or debit card numbers of individuals that submit questions through our website’s “contact us” page.
Categories of Personal Information That We Collect
To Whom We Disclose Personal Information for Business Purpose
Identifiers – such as name, postal address, phone number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, internet protocol (IP) address, device ID, email address, account name, signature, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers.
Advertising networks
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Data analytics providers
Data brokers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Internet service providers
Joint marketing partners
Operating systems and platforms
Other Service Providers
Payment processors and financial institutions
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Social networks
Financial information –
such as bank account number, credit or debit card number, or other financial information.
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Other Service Providers
Payment Processors and financial institutions
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Medical / health insurance information –
such as information from a healthcare provider regarding an individual’s medical history, mental or physical condition, or treatment;  an individual’s insurance policy number or subscriber identification number, any unique identifier used by a health insurer to identify the individual, or any information in the individual’s application and claims history.
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Other Service Providers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Protected characteristics –
such as race, gender, physical or mental disability, and religion.
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Other Service Providers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Commercial information –
such as information about products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies.
Advertising networks
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Data analytics providers
Data brokers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Internet service providers
Joint marketing partners
Operating systems and platforms
Other Service Providers
Payment processors and financial institutions
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Social networks
Network activity data –
internet or other electronic network activity information, such as browsing history, search history, and information regarding an individual’s interaction with an internet website, application, or advertisement.
Advertising networks
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Data analytics providers
Data brokers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Internet service providers
Joint marketing partners
Operating systems and platforms
Other Service Providers
Payment processors and financial institutions
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Social networks
Biometric information –
such as fingerprint, face print or voice print.
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Other Service Providers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Geolocation data –
such as precise physical location.
Advertising networks
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Data analytics providers
Data brokers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Internet service providers
Joint marketing partners
Operating systems and platforms
Other Service Providers
Payment processors and financial institutions
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Social networks
Electronic and sensory data –
such as audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information (e.g., pictures, a recording of a customer service call, security video surveillance footage).
Affiliates or subsidiaries
Business partners
Other Service Providers
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Professional/employment information –
such as occupation and professional references.
Government entities, as may be needed to comply with law or prevent illegal activity
Professional services organizations, this may include auditors and law firms
Social networks
Close
Thanks!
Thank you for contacting us!
Our group will review and follow up within 72 hours.
Thanks for your interest!
The TramThe Cliff LodgeSeventyOneSnow ReportMeetingsOktoberfest
Close
Close
